{
  "1": {
    "question": "In what year was the current Roberto Clemente Bridge built?",
    "answer": "1928",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "2": {
    "question": "When is first quarter Payroll Tax due in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "31-May",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "3": {
    "question": "What is Pittsburgh's MLB team called?",
    "answer": "Pittsburgh Pirates.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "4": {
    "question": "What were the Steelers originally called?",
    "answer": "Pittsburgh Pirates",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "5": {
    "question": "How many people died in the Allegheny Arsenal explosion during the Civil War?",
    "answer": "78",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "6": {
    "question": "What year was Pittsburgh incorporated?",
    "answer": "1816",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "7": {
    "question": "What is the minimum combined sales tax rate in Pittsburgh as of 2025?",
    "answer": "7%",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "8": {
    "question": "What is Pittsburgh's police overtime budget?",
    "answer": "$15 million",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "9": {
    "question": "In what year was Bloomfield annexed by the City of Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "1868",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "10": {
    "question": "What year did the Jack Rabbit roller coaster open at Kennywood?",
    "answer": "1920",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "11": {
    "question": "In what year did the Boulevard of the Allies open, providing a direct link from Squirrel Hill to downtown Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "1927",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "12": {
    "question": "What is Pittsburgh's Real Estate Tax revenue?",
    "answer": "$152 million (projected 2025).",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "13": {
    "question": "What park is Downtown Pittsburgh's state park?",
    "answer": "Point State Park",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "14": {
    "question": "In what year did Botany Hall at Phipps Conservatory complete construction?",
    "answer": "1902",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "15": {
    "question": "How many Super Bowls have the Steelers won?",
    "answer": "6",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "16": {
    "question": "What rivers form the Ohio River in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "The Allegheny and Monongahela Rivers",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "17": {
    "question": "What two rivers meet in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "Allegheny River and Monongahela River",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "18": {
    "question": "What chapter governs Pittsburgh's Payroll Expense Tax?",
    "answer": "Chapter 258",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "19": {
    "question": "What is Pittsburgh's biggest free arts festival?",
    "answer": "Dollar Bank Three Rivers Arts Festival",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "20": {
    "question": "When was Pittsburgh incorporated as a borough?",
    "answer": "April 22, 1794.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "21": {
    "question": "What is Pittsburgh's nickname related to steel?",
    "answer": "Steel City",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "22": {
    "question": "What baseball stadium is rated best in America by Travel and Leisure?",
    "answer": "PNC Park",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "23": {
    "question": "Who founded Carnegie Technical Schools?",
    "answer": "Andrew Carnegie",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "24": {
    "question": "What former church is a music venue?",
    "answer": "Mr. Smalls Theatre (formerly St. Ann\u2019s Catholic Church).",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "25": {
    "question": "What is the area in square miles of Squirrel Hill as stated by the Squirrel Hill Historical Society?",
    "answer": "3.89 square miles",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "26": {
    "question": "When was Pittsburgh incorporated as a city?",
    "answer": "March 18, 1816.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "27": {
    "question": "What county is Pittsburgh the seat of?",
    "answer": "Allegheny County",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "28": {
    "question": "What was Pittsburgh's 2020 population?",
    "answer": "302,971",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "29": {
    "question": "When was Andrew Mellon's birth year?",
    "answer": "1855",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "30": {
    "question": "When is second quarter LST due in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "31-Jul",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "31": {
    "question": "What was the original cost to raise funds to repair and reopen the Duquesne Incline in 1963?",
    "answer": "$15,000 ",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "32": {
    "question": "What year did the Parkway and Squirrel Hill Tunnel open?",
    "answer": "1953",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "33": {
    "question": "What is Pittsburgh's Payroll Expense Tax rate?",
    "answer": "0.55%",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "34": {
    "question": "What is Pittsburgh's annual Local Services Tax?",
    "answer": "$52 per year.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "35": {
    "question": "How many neighborhoods make up North Shore?",
    "answer": "18",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "36": {
    "question": "Who founded Lawrenceville in 1814?",
    "answer": "William Barclay Foster",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "37": {
    "question": "When is first quarter LST due in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "April 30.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "38": {
    "question": "In what year were railroad tracks removed from Liberty Avenue downtown, causing produce merchants to relocate to the Strip District?",
    "answer": "1906",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "39": {
    "question": "Who laid out Pittsburgh in 1764?",
    "answer": "Colonel John Campbell",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "40": {
    "question": "What is Pittsburgh's 2025 operating budget?",
    "answer": "$665.6 million",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "41": {
    "question": "What stadium do the Steelers play in?",
    "answer": "Acrisure Stadium",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "42": {
    "question": "How many square miles is Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "58.3 square miles",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "43": {
    "question": "Where is Carnegie Mellon's main campus located?",
    "answer": "Pittsburgh\u2019s Oakland neighborhood, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "44": {
    "question": "When was CMU-Qatar established?",
    "answer": "2004",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "45": {
    "question": "What museum features Roberto Clemente memorabilia?",
    "answer": "The Clemente Museum",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "46": {
    "question": "How many neighborhoods does Pittsburgh have?",
    "answer": "90",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "47": {
    "question": "On what date did the Duquesne Incline open to the public?",
    "answer": "May 20, 1877",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "48": {
    "question": "What Kennywood food is most iconic?",
    "answer": "Potato Patch fries",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "49": {
    "question": "How many bridges does Pittsburgh have?",
    "answer": "446",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "50": {
    "question": "What year did Acrisure Stadium open?",
    "answer": "2001",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "51": {
    "question": "How many years is the Pittsburgh Controller's term?",
    "answer": "4 years",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "52": {
    "question": "How many display rooms did Phipps Conservatory originally have when it opened?",
    "answer": "9",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "53": {
    "question": "What is the income threshold below which employees are exempt from Pittsburgh's Local Services Tax in 2025?",
    "answer": "$12,000 ",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "54": {
    "question": "What colors do Pittsburgh sports teams share?",
    "answer": "Black and gold",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "55": {
    "question": "Who began steel production using Bessemer process?",
    "answer": "Andrew Carnegie",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "56": {
    "question": "On what date did Frick Park officially open to the public?",
    "answer": "June 25, 1927.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "57": {
    "question": "What is Pittsburgh's Amusement Tax rate?",
    "answer": "5%",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "58": {
    "question": "What festival is named number one in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "Picklesburgh",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "59": {
    "question": "How many photographic negatives does Carnegie hold?",
    "answer": "Approximately 80,000",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "60": {
    "question": "What is the length of the Monongahela River in miles?",
    "answer": "130 miles",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "61": {
    "question": "What neighborhood does Mayor Gainey live in?",
    "answer": "Lincoln-Lemington",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "62": {
    "question": "When was the American Federation of Labor born in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "November 15, 1881.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "63": {
    "question": "How long is the Ohio River from Pittsburgh to where it meets the Mississippi River?",
    "answer": "981 miles",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "64": {
    "question": "When does Pittsburgh host the NFL Draft?",
    "answer": "April 23\ufffd?5, 2026",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "65": {
    "question": "How many Downtown Pittsburgh restaurants exist?",
    "answer": "100",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "66": {
    "question": "Who expelled the French in 1758?",
    "answer": "General John Forbes",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "67": {
    "question": "What year does Pittsburgh host NFL Draft?",
    "answer": "2026",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "68": {
    "question": "On what date did Phipps Conservatory open to the public?",
    "answer": "December 7, 1893",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "69": {
    "question": "What is Pittsburgh's total general fund headcount?",
    "answer": "3,278.75 employees.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "70": {
    "question": "When did Carnegie Tech begin granting bachelor's degrees?",
    "answer": "1912",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "71": {
    "question": "When did the Carnegie-Mellon merger occur?",
    "answer": "1967",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "72": {
    "question": "How many acres did Henry Clay Frick originally bequeath to the City of Pittsburgh for Frick Park?",
    "answer": "151 acres",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "73": {
    "question": "On what date did the Monongahela Incline open for service?",
    "answer": "May 28, 1870.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "74": {
    "question": "What is the height rise of the Duquesne Incline in feet?",
    "answer": "400 feet.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "75": {
    "question": "What year was the Pittsburgh Academy founded?",
    "answer": "1787",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "76": {
    "question": "What year did Pittsburgh suffer its worst flood?",
    "answer": "1936",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "77": {
    "question": "What's the returned check fee in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "$30.00 ",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "78": {
    "question": "When was Carnegie Mellon founded?",
    "answer": "1900",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "79": {
    "question": "In what year did Kennywood purchase Idlewild amusement park?",
    "answer": "1983",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "80": {
    "question": "When was the University of Pittsburgh chartered?",
    "answer": "February 28, 1787",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "81": {
    "question": "On what date was the Roberto Clemente Bridge first lit with architectural lighting?",
    "answer": "20-Nov-02",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "82": {
    "question": "Who founded the Pittsburgh Academy?",
    "answer": "Hugh Henry Brackenridge",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "83": {
    "question": "Who developed the polio vaccine at Pitt?",
    "answer": "Jonas Salk",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "84": {
    "question": "How many City Council members are in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "9",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "85": {
    "question": "When is fourth quarter LST due in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "January 30.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "86": {
    "question": "How many independently elected citywide offices exist in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "2",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "87": {
    "question": "Who invented the Terrible Towel?",
    "answer": "Myron Cope",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "88": {
    "question": "When did the Senator John Heinz History Center open in the Strip District?",
    "answer": "29-Apr-96",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "89": {
    "question": "What company built the current Roberto Clemente Bridge?",
    "answer": "American Bridge Company",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "90": {
    "question": "What is Pittsburgh's NHL team?",
    "answer": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "91": {
    "question": "What is Pittsburgh's largest revenue source?",
    "answer": "Earned income (wage) tax",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "92": {
    "question": "What is Lawrenceville's primary zip code?",
    "answer": "15201",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "93": {
    "question": "What year was the Whiskey Rebellion?",
    "answer": "1794",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "94": {
    "question": "What year did it become Carnegie Mellon University?",
    "answer": "1967",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "95": {
    "question": "When was the School of Computer Science opened?",
    "answer": "1988",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "96": {
    "question": "When is fourth quarter Payroll Tax due in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "February 28 (of the following year).",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "97": {
    "question": "What is Pittsburgh's projected year-end fund balance?",
    "answer": "$146 million.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "98": {
    "question": "How many EMS employees are budgeted in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "217",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "99": {
    "question": "What merged with Carnegie Tech in 1967?",
    "answer": "The Mellon Institute of Industrial Research",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "100": {
    "question": "When is third quarter Payroll Tax due in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "November 30.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "101": {
    "question": "In what neighborhood is Stage AE?",
    "answer": "North Shore",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "102": {
    "question": "What was the name of the mattress warehouse that becamse Mattress Factory's first site in 1975?",
    "answer": "Stearns & Foster",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "103": {
    "question": "How many stories is the Warhol museum?",
    "answer": "Seven stories",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "104": {
    "question": "On what day of the week is the Frick closed?",
    "answer": "Monday",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "105": {
    "question": "How may photographs, prints, and negatives does the Detre Library & Archives have in its collection?",
    "answer": "700,000.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "106": {
    "question": "On how many days of the week is the Detre Library & Archives open?",
    "answer": "4 days",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "107": {
    "question": "At which venue will The Rocky Horror Show appear in October and November?",
    "answer": "Greer Cabaret Theater",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "108": {
    "question": "In what year did ground break on construction of the August Wilson African American Cultural Center?",
    "answer": "2006",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "109": {
    "question": "Who do I contact to discuss accessibility accomodations for volunteers at the PSO?",
    "answer": "Amy Cale Program Manager \ufffd?acale@pittsburghsymphony.org",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "110": {
    "question": "What is the phone number of the PSO box office?",
    "answer": "412-392-4900",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "111": {
    "question": "What is the age cutoff for free tickets at the Heinz History Center?",
    "answer": "17 and under",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "112": {
    "question": "What was the name of the precursor to today's Carnegie magazine?",
    "answer": "Bulletin of the Carnegie Institute",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "113": {
    "question": "On what ancestral lands does the Frick Pittsburgh occupy?",
    "answer": "Haudenosaunee, Lenape, Osage, and Shawnee peoples",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "114": {
    "question": "How many seats are in the Buhl Planetarium?",
    "answer": "150",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "115": {
    "question": "What condition will cause the Kamin Science center to close on Sundays?",
    "answer": "Steelers home games at Acrisure Stadium.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "116": {
    "question": "The Heinz History Center is affiliated with which federal institution?",
    "answer": "Smithsonian Institution",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "117": {
    "question": "The Frick Pittsburgh is located in which neighborhood?",
    "answer": "Point Breeze",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "118": {
    "question": "What was the Heinz History Center's Charity Navigator rating?",
    "answer": "Four-Star (97%)",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "119": {
    "question": "When does the Grable Visitor center close each day?",
    "answer": "5:00 PM",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "120": {
    "question": "What is the square footage of the George R. White opera studio?",
    "answer": "5,568 sq ft",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "121": {
    "question": "The Powerdermill Nature reserve is renowned for what research?",
    "answer": "Avian research\u2014especially long\u2011term bird banding",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "122": {
    "question": "What is the theme of Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre's 2025-2026 season?",
    "answer": "The Dream Season",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "123": {
    "question": "Does the pittsburgh symphony orchestrator have more first or second chair violinists?",
    "answer": "Same number (one each).",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "124": {
    "question": "Which type of Pittsburgh Opera ticket pass gives one unlimited access to the opera at a low monthly fee?",
    "answer": "Opus Pass.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "125": {
    "question": "Who is the associate conductor leading the Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra concerts at Heinz Hall during Light Up Night 2025?",
    "answer": "Moon Doh",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "126": {
    "question": "Which of the following is not a real learning program associated witht he Pittsburgh symphony orchestra? Side-by-Side, Schooltime, Play Your Heart Out, Fiddlesticks Musical Exploration",
    "answer": "Play Your Heart Out",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "127": {
    "question": "What park is Pittsburgh's Fort Pitt Museum is located in?",
    "answer": "Point State Park",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "128": {
    "question": "The oldest car of what make (brand) is located at Pittsburgh's \"People Museum\"?",
    "answer": "Jeep",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "129": {
    "question": "What organization did the Pittsburgh Post Gazette laud as \"the single greatest creative force in Pittsburgh because of its spirit of reinvention\"?",
    "answer": "Pittsburgh Cultural Trust",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "130": {
    "question": "In what year did PSO celebrate its 125th anniversary?",
    "answer": "2021",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "131": {
    "question": "How much does it cost to attend the Heinz History Center with a student ID?",
    "answer": "$11 ",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "132": {
    "question": "How many city blocks does Pittsburgh's Cultural District span?",
    "answer": "14 city blocks",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "133": {
    "question": "What is the cost of admission to the Detre Library & Archives?",
    "answer": "Free",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "134": {
    "question": "In which country was the music director of the Pittsburgh orchestra born?",
    "answer": "Austria",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "135": {
    "question": "What is the starting price for a children's ticket to one of the Pittsburgh Opera's mainstage shows?",
    "answer": "$7.50 ",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "136": {
    "question": "What is the title of the individual who wins Picklesburgh's pickle juice drinking competition?",
    "answer": "Mayor of Picklesburgh",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "137": {
    "question": "Who is the Presient and CEO of the August Wilson African American Cultural Center?",
    "answer": "Janis Burley",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "138": {
    "question": "Which sports exhibit is coming to Kamin Science Center in December 2025?",
    "answer": "Sports360",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "139": {
    "question": "How to find the Carnegie Museum of Art on instagram (username)?",
    "answer": "@carnegiemuseumofart",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "140": {
    "question": "When did Roberto Clemente join the Pittsburgh Pirates?",
    "answer": "November 22, 1954.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "141": {
    "question": "What are the two types of space rentals available through the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust",
    "answer": "Host an Event; Put on a Show",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "142": {
    "question": "In which PSO corporate partnership tier is Lighthouse Electric?",
    "answer": "Up to $2,500.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "143": {
    "question": "What is Pennsylvania's largest history museum?",
    "answer": "Senator John Heinz History Center",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "144": {
    "question": "Which biblically-related production does Pittsburgh Opera rent out?",
    "answer": "Samson & Dalila",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "145": {
    "question": "Which Pittsburgh museum displays contemporary Jewish art?",
    "answer": "American Jewish Museum.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "146": {
    "question": "In what month will Chorus auditions take place for the Pittsburgh Opera's 2026-27 season?",
    "answer": "May",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "147": {
    "question": "Who is the secretary officer on the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust Board of Trustees",
    "answer": "Nicholas J. Gigante",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "148": {
    "question": "Which is the most comprehensive single-artist museum in the world?",
    "answer": "The Andy Warhol Museum",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "149": {
    "question": "In which neighborhood was Pittsburgh's planetarium originally located?",
    "answer": "Allegheny Center.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "150": {
    "question": "Polar World is the largest exhibit on what society?",
    "answer": "Inuit society",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "151": {
    "question": "What does 'Acupuncture' refer to in the context of the Pittsburgh skyline",
    "answer": "The rooftop light sculpture atop the Mattress Factory museum.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "152": {
    "question": "Who financed the Heinz Architectural Center at its launch?",
    "answer": "Drue Heinz (Mrs. Henry J. Heinz II)",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "153": {
    "question": "Where is Charles \"Teenie\" Harris' Archive currently on exhibit?",
    "answer": "Carnegie Museum of Art, Scaife Gallery 7, Pittsburgh.)",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "154": {
    "question": "The Warhol museum contains approximately how many paintings?",
    "answer": "Approximately 900",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "155": {
    "question": "Where is the Orwell film playing in October?",
    "answer": "Harris Theater, 809 Liberty Ave, Pittsburgh.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "156": {
    "question": "Which musical instrument is available at an additional cost for event bookings at the Goerge R. White opera studio?",
    "answer": "Piano",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "157": {
    "question": "How to find the Carnegie Museum of Art on youtube (username)?",
    "answer": "@CarnegieMuseumofArt",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "158": {
    "question": "In what venue was the Pittsburgh Opera's first production?",
    "answer": "Carnegie Music Hall",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "159": {
    "question": "How tall was dinosaur fossil was the first added to the Carnegie Museum's collection?",
    "answer": "12 feet (at the hips).",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "160": {
    "question": "What major architectural center opened in Pittsburgh in 1993?",
    "answer": "Heinz Architectural Center",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "161": {
    "question": "How many contrabassoonists are in the pittsburgh orchestra?",
    "answer": "1",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "162": {
    "question": "What is the street address of Pittsburgh's Mattress Factory?",
    "answer": "509 Jacksonia St., Pittsburgh, PA 15212.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "163": {
    "question": "Artifacts from what famous TV set are displayed at Pittsburgh's \"People Museum\"?",
    "answer": "Mister Rogers' Neighborhood",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "164": {
    "question": "Who was the International Classical Music award's artist of the year in 2018?",
    "answer": "Manfred Honeck",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "165": {
    "question": "What is the last day of the Noises Off show?",
    "answer": "October 19, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "166": {
    "question": "In its guidance on logo use, does the Pitttsburgh Cultural Trust prefer the horizontal or vertical logo layout?",
    "answer": "Horizontal",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "167": {
    "question": "How many photographs are in the Warhol museum?",
    "answer": "4,000 photographs",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "168": {
    "question": "Where are artists in residence at Mattress Factory likely to live?",
    "answer": "North Taylor Avenue (e.g. 503 North Taylor Ave).",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "169": {
    "question": "In what year was Dinosaur Hall unveiled?",
    "answer": "1907",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "170": {
    "question": "What type of dinosaur fossil was the first added to the Carnegie Museum's collection?",
    "answer": "Diplodocus (Diplodocus carnegii)",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "171": {
    "question": "What is the street aderess of the Carnegie Museum of Art?",
    "answer": "4400 Forbes Avenue",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "172": {
    "question": "In what year did old residents of Pittsburgh and Western PA establish a society to help preserve local history?",
    "answer": "1879",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "173": {
    "question": "How does the Mattress Factory define artistic quality?",
    "answer": "Through the process of making, not just the product.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "174": {
    "question": "When was Mattress Factory founded?",
    "answer": "1977",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "175": {
    "question": "Which submarine is in the Ohio river beside downtown Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "USS Requin (SS-481)",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "176": {
    "question": "How many architecture related objects are in the Heinz Architectural center's collection?",
    "answer": "Approximately 6,000",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "177": {
    "question": "The famous pop art painting, \"Campbell's Soup Cans\", is on display in what Pittsburgh museum?",
    "answer": "The Andy Warhol Museum",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "178": {
    "question": "At which venue does the Pittsburgh Opera present its largest productions?",
    "answer": "Benedum Center for the Performing Arts",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "179": {
    "question": "How much are supernumerary positions paid at the Pittsburgh Opera?",
    "answer": "$100 honorarium.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "180": {
    "question": "When was the Heinz Architectural Center created?",
    "answer": "1990",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "181": {
    "question": "In which year did the Powdermill Nature Reserve open?",
    "answer": "1956",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "182": {
    "question": "What is the Clemente Museum's instagram handle?",
    "answer": "@theclementemuseum",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "183": {
    "question": "What Drop-in Session at Carnegie Museum of Art is happening on Fri, Oct 10, in the morning?",
    "answer": "Carnegie Lab (10 a.m.)",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "184": {
    "question": "What is Amanda Dunyak Gillen's role at The Frick?",
    "answer": "Executive Director",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "185": {
    "question": "Who to contact to discuss issues of Rights and Reproduction regarding images from the Warhol collection?",
    "answer": "rights@warhol.org",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "186": {
    "question": "How old do you need to be to volunteer with the PSO in the default case?",
    "answer": "18 years old.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "187": {
    "question": "How may books, pamphlets, and monographs does the Detre Library & Archives have in its collection?",
    "answer": "40,000.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "188": {
    "question": "In what year was the pop district in Pittsburgh launched?",
    "answer": "2022",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "189": {
    "question": "In which neighborhood is the Pittsburgh Opera currently located?",
    "answer": "Strip District",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "190": {
    "question": "In what year was the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust founded?",
    "answer": "1984",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "191": {
    "question": "How many visitors does the Pittsburgh Cultural District attract annually?",
    "answer": "Over 2,000,000 visitors annually",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "192": {
    "question": "How many blocks does the Pop District span on Pittsburgh's North Shore?",
    "answer": "6 blocks",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "193": {
    "question": "What is the longest-running exhibition of international art in North America?",
    "answer": "Carnegie International",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "194": {
    "question": "Does the Clemente museum have walk-in hours?",
    "answer": "No\u2014only ticketed tours/open houses; no walk-ins.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "195": {
    "question": "Which symphony was President and CEO Tourangeau at before coming to Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "Utah Symphony | Utah Opera",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "196": {
    "question": "What is Powdermill Nature reserve named after?",
    "answer": "A historic gunpowder mill (\"powder mill\").",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "197": {
    "question": "When did the Founding Five found the Pittsburgh Opera?",
    "answer": "1939",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "198": {
    "question": "What is the maximum bag size allowed into Pittsburgh Cultural Trust events?",
    "answer": "16\" x 16\" x 8\".",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "199": {
    "question": "In what building does the Pittsburgh orchestra perform?",
    "answer": "Heinz Hall for the Performing Arts",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "200": {
    "question": "Who opened the 'palace of culture' in 1895",
    "answer": "Andrew Carnegie",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "201": {
    "question": "What song is played during the fourth quarter when the Steelers need a big stop?",
    "answer": "Renegade by Styx",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "202": {
    "question": "On what dates will the Penguins play in the NHL Global Series in Stockholm?",
    "answer": "November 14 and 16, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "203": {
    "question": "When is the Pittsburgh Vintage Grand Prix held?",
    "answer": "Annually in July",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "204": {
    "question": "What percentage of Penguins home games are played on weekends in 2025-26?",
    "answer": "53%",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "205": {
    "question": "When will the Riverhounds ownership group start a USL W League team?",
    "answer": "2025 season",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "206": {
    "question": "When is the Steelers game on Monday Night Football in 2025?",
    "answer": "Monday, December 15, 2025 at 8:15 PM ET.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "207": {
    "question": "When did the Pittsburgh Pirates return to the postseason after a 20-season losing streak?",
    "answer": "September 23, 2013.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "208": {
    "question": "When did Mario Lemieux announce his retirement from the Pittsburgh Penguins?",
    "answer": "January 24, 2006.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "209": {
    "question": "Where can you find the Immaculate Reception Monument to celebrate the Pittsburgh Steelers?",
    "answer": "On West General Robinson Street near Stage AE, outside Acrisure Stadium (the North Shore site of the play).",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "210": {
    "question": "When is the Steelers game against the Buffalo Bills in 2025?",
    "answer": "November 30, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "211": {
    "question": "What does the inverted \"Y\" on the Pittsburgh Pirates' City Connect uniform represent?",
    "answer": "The convergence of the Allegheny, Monongahela, and Ohio Rivers",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "212": {
    "question": "When was Mike Sullivan named head coach of the Pittsburgh Penguins?",
    "answer": "December 12, 2015.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "213": {
    "question": "When is the game between the Washington Capitals and Pittsburgh Penguins scheduled?",
    "answer": "November 6, 2025, 7:30 PM ET",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "214": {
    "question": "When is the game between the Indianapolis Colts and Pittsburgh Steelers scheduled?",
    "answer": "Sunday, Nov. 2, 2025, 1:00 PM ET.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "215": {
    "question": "When does Pitt host Eastern Michigan for men's basketball in 2025-26?",
    "answer": "10-Nov-25",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "216": {
    "question": "When did the Pittsburgh Pirates leave Forbes Field?",
    "answer": "June 28 1970",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "217": {
    "question": "What is the address of the Pittsburgh Penguins' arena?",
    "answer": "1001 Fifth Avenue, Pittsburgh, PA 15219",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "218": {
    "question": "When is the game between the Columbus Blue Jackets and Pittsburgh Penguins scheduled?",
    "answer": "October 25, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "219": {
    "question": "Where will the Pittsburgh Penguins play against the New Jersey Devils on November 8, 2025?",
    "answer": "Prudential Center, Newark, New Jersey.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "220": {
    "question": "When does Pitt play West Virginia in the Backyard Brawl for basketball in 2025-26?",
    "answer": "13-Nov-25",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "221": {
    "question": "Who is the head coach of the Pittsburgh Steelers?",
    "answer": "Mike Tomlin",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "222": {
    "question": "How many Super Bowls have the Pittsburgh Steelers won?",
    "answer": "6",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "223": {
    "question": "When was Dan Muse hired as head coach of the Pittsburgh Penguins?",
    "answer": "4-Jun-25",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "224": {
    "question": "When do the Penguins host the Edmonton Oilers in December 2025?",
    "answer": "December 16, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "225": {
    "question": "What is the address of the Pittsburgh Steelers' Acrisure Stadium?",
    "answer": "100 Art Rooney Ave Pittsburgh PA 15212.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "226": {
    "question": "How many preseason games do the Penguins play in 2025?",
    "answer": "7",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "227": {
    "question": "Who is the Pittsburgh Pirates broadcaster known for the phrase \"Raise The Jolly Roger\"?",
    "answer": "Greg Brown",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "228": {
    "question": "What is the name of the scholarship fund established in memory of the late founder of the Steelers?",
    "answer": "Art Rooney Scholarship Fund",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "229": {
    "question": "How many straight weeks will the Steelers play without a break after their bye week in 2025?",
    "answer": "13",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "230": {
    "question": "Who originally wrote and recorded the Steelers fight song \"Here We Go\"?",
    "answer": "Roger Wood",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "231": {
    "question": "In what year were the Pittsburgh Pirates established?",
    "answer": "1882",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "232": {
    "question": "Name one NCAA Division 1 university located in Pittsburgh.",
    "answer": "University of Pittsburgh.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "233": {
    "question": "What is the name of the Pittsburgh Penguins' AHL affiliate team?",
    "answer": "Wilkes-Barre/Scranton Penguins",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "234": {
    "question": "Who has been the Pittsburgh Penguins' public address announcer since 2009?",
    "answer": "Ryan Mill",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "235": {
    "question": "Where are the home bouts for The Steel Hurtin\u201aThe Steel Beamers, and the Blitzburgh Bombers held?",
    "answer": "Pittsburgh Indoor Sports Arena (PISA), 22 Rich Hill Rd, Cheswick, PA",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "236": {
    "question": "Where is the game between the Miami Dolphins and Pittsburgh Steelers on December 15, 2025, being played?",
    "answer": "Acrisure Stadium, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "237": {
    "question": "Who holds the Pittsburgh Pirates' career record for most home runs?",
    "answer": "Willie Stargell",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "238": {
    "question": "Who is the manager of the Pittsburgh Pirates?",
    "answer": "Don Kelly",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "239": {
    "question": "What are the official colors of the Pittsburgh Steelers?",
    "answer": "Black and gold",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "240": {
    "question": "What is the home stadium of the Pittsburgh Steelers football team?",
    "answer": "Acrisure Stadium",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "241": {
    "question": "What is the capacity of Highmark Stadium?",
    "answer": "5,000",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "242": {
    "question": "When will the Pittsburgh Penguins relaunch their Hall of Fame?",
    "answer": "25-Oct-25",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "243": {
    "question": "When was The Pirate Parrot mascot introduced for the Pittsburgh Pirates?",
    "answer": "1979",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "244": {
    "question": "When did Highmark Stadium open?",
    "answer": "13-Apr-13",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "245": {
    "question": "When did the Pittsburgh Steelers play their first playoff game in franchise history?",
    "answer": "21-Dec-47",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "246": {
    "question": "Where is the Pittsburgh Penguins vs San Jose Sharks game on October 18, 2025, being held?",
    "answer": "SAP Center at San Jose.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "247": {
    "question": "Which Pittsburgh-based Gaelic football team won both the Midwest and National titles in 2011?",
    "answer": "Pittsburgh Celtics",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "248": {
    "question": "Which stadium is home to the University of Pittsburgh Panthers football team?",
    "answer": "Acrisure Stadium",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "249": {
    "question": "Who created the Terrible Towel and in what year?",
    "answer": "Myron Cope, 1975",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "250": {
    "question": "Which NHL team is based in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania?",
    "answer": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "251": {
    "question": "Name three NCAA Division 1 universities in Pittsburgh.",
    "answer": "University of Pittsburgh; Duquesne University; Robert Morris University",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "252": {
    "question": "When does Pitt play Providence in an exhibition game for 2025-26?",
    "answer": "October 19 2025 (2:00 p.m. ET)",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "253": {
    "question": "When was the Pittsburgh Passion women's full-contact football team formed?",
    "answer": "2002",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "254": {
    "question": "Which teams are the primary divisional rivals of the Pittsburgh Steelers?",
    "answer": "Baltimore Ravens; Cincinnati Bengals; Cleveland Browns.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "255": {
    "question": "Who was awarded the Conn Smythe Trophy when the Penguins won the Stanley Cup in 2016?",
    "answer": "Sidney Crosby.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "256": {
    "question": "How can college students get discounted tickets for Pittsburgh Penguins games?",
    "answer": "Through the Penguins' GetGo Student Rush\u2014verify a .edu email and buy same-day Student Rush tickets (sign up by texting RUSH to 412-534-6266 or via the Penguins app).",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "257": {
    "question": "Who was hired as the Pittsburgh Steelers head coach in 1969?",
    "answer": "Chuck Noll",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "258": {
    "question": "What is the combined 2024 win percentage of the Steelers' 2025 opponents?",
    "answer": "0.526",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "259": {
    "question": "When do the Penguins host the Carolina Hurricanes on December 30, 2025?",
    "answer": "7:00 PM ET. ",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "260": {
    "question": "Which Pittsburgh team competes in the Ultimate Frisbee Association?",
    "answer": "Pittsburgh Thunderbirds",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "261": {
    "question": "When is the Penguins' traditional Thanksgiving Eve game in 2025?",
    "answer": "26-Nov-25",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "262": {
    "question": "When is the game between the Cleveland Browns and Pittsburgh Steelers scheduled?",
    "answer": "October 12, 2025, 1:00 PM ET.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "263": {
    "question": "Who designed PNC Park?",
    "answer": "HOK Sport (now Populous)",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "264": {
    "question": "When do the Penguins play the Montreal Canadiens at home in December 2025?",
    "answer": "December 11 and December 21, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "265": {
    "question": "How many World Series championships have the Pittsburgh Pirates won?",
    "answer": "5",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "266": {
    "question": "When did the Three Rivers Stadium open?",
    "answer": "July 16 1970",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "267": {
    "question": "How much money have the proceeds from the Terrible Towel helped raise for the school in Coraopolis?",
    "answer": "Over $9.5 million",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "268": {
    "question": "Who founded the Pittsburgh Steelers and in what year?",
    "answer": "Art Rooney Sr., 1933",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "269": {
    "question": "Where will the Pittsburgh Penguins play on October 14, 2025?",
    "answer": "Honda Center (Anaheim, California)",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "270": {
    "question": "Who is the offensive coordinator for the Pittsburgh Steelers in the 2025 season?",
    "answer": "Arthur Smith",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "271": {
    "question": "Who was the manager of the Pittsburgh Pirates during their 1971 World Series championship?",
    "answer": "Danny Murtaugh",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "272": {
    "question": "How many times have the Pittsburgh Pirates won the World Series?",
    "answer": "5",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "273": {
    "question": "Where is the Steelers Hall of Honor Museum located?",
    "answer": "Acrisure Stadium, above the Steelers Pro Shop (Gate B), Pittsburgh, PA",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "274": {
    "question": "How many Division I varsity teams does the University of Pittsburgh sponsor?",
    "answer": "19",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "275": {
    "question": "When did the Steelers Hall of Honor Museum open?",
    "answer": "11-Nov-22",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "276": {
    "question": "Who created the Terrible Towel for the Pittsburgh Steelers?",
    "answer": "Myron Cope",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "277": {
    "question": "What are the co-captains for Steelers Style?",
    "answer": "DeShon Elliott and DK Metcalf.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "278": {
    "question": "What foundation did the Pittsburgh Steelers help establish with an initial contribution of $1 million to support brain injury research?",
    "answer": "The Chuck Noll Foundation for Brain Injury Research",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "279": {
    "question": "Who holds the Pittsburgh Penguins franchise record for the most points scored by a defenseman?",
    "answer": "Kris Letang",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "280": {
    "question": "When did the Pittsburgh Penguins win back-to-back Stanley Cup championships?",
    "answer": "1991\ufffd?992 and 2016\ufffd?017",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "281": {
    "question": "How many sets of back-to-back games will the Penguins play in 2025-26?",
    "answer": "16",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "282": {
    "question": "Who succeeded Chuck Noll as head coach of the Pittsburgh Steelers in 1992?",
    "answer": "Bill Cowher.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "283": {
    "question": "In what year did the Pittsburgh Pirates win their first World Series?",
    "answer": "1909",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "284": {
    "question": "Who holds the Pittsburgh Penguins franchise record for most points scored by a defenseman?",
    "answer": "Kris Letang.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "285": {
    "question": "Which architectural firm designed Acrisure Stadium?",
    "answer": "Populous",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "286": {
    "question": "How many home run balls have splashed into the Allegheny River from PNC Park?",
    "answer": "84",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "287": {
    "question": "Which university in Pittsburgh is a member of the Atlantic Coast Conference in college football?",
    "answer": "University of Pittsburgh",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "288": {
    "question": "What annual road race in Pittsburgh attracts nearly 10,000 athletes and has been ranked as a Top 20 Multi-Race Event by USA Track & Field's publication On The Roads?",
    "answer": "Richard S. Caliguiri City of Pittsburgh Great Race",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "289": {
    "question": "What is the address of PNC Park where the Pittsburgh Pirates play?",
    "answer": "115 Federal Street, Pittsburgh, PA 15212",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "290": {
    "question": "When is the game between the Montreal Canadiens and Pittsburgh Penguins scheduled?",
    "answer": "December 11, 2025, 7:00 PM ET",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "291": {
    "question": "Where is the Pittsburgh Penguins' home arena located?",
    "answer": "1001 Fifth Avenue, Pittsburgh, PA 15219.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "292": {
    "question": "When did the Pittsburgh Pirates adopt their current black and gold color scheme?",
    "answer": "1948",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "293": {
    "question": "What is the nickname of the Pittsburgh Steelers?",
    "answer": "Steel Curtain",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "294": {
    "question": "When did the Pittsburgh Pirates return to the postseason after a 20-season losing record?",
    "answer": "2013",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "295": {
    "question": "Who is the General Manager of the Pittsburgh Pirates?",
    "answer": "Ben Cherington",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "296": {
    "question": "What do the colors in the Pittsburgh Steelers logo represent?",
    "answer": "Yellow = coal; red = iron ore; blue = steel scrap",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "297": {
    "question": "In which years did the Pittsburgh Penguins win the Stanley Cup championships?",
    "answer": "1991, 1992, 2009, 2016, 2017.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "298": {
    "question": "What are the traditional colors for Pittsburgh sports teams?",
    "answer": "Black and gold",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "299": {
    "question": "When is the game between the Buffalo Sabres and Pittsburgh Penguins scheduled?",
    "answer": "26-Nov-25",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "300": {
    "question": "Who is the first-string quarterback for the Pittsburgh Steelers?",
    "answer": "Aaron Rodgers",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "301": {
    "question": "What Costa Rican botanist is featured in an exhibition at Hunt Institute through December 17, 2025?",
    "answer": "Rafael Lucas Rodr\u00edguez Caballero",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "302": {
    "question": "When does Phipps Spring Flower Show open in 2025?",
    "answer": "March 22, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "303": {
    "question": "When does the 59th Carnegie International end?",
    "answer": "3-Jan-27",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "304": {
    "question": "What weekly meditation session takes place on Sundays at CMU?",
    "answer": "Heartfulness Meditation",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "305": {
    "question": "What are the exact dates for Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre's The Nutcracker performances in 2025?",
    "answer": "December 5, 6, 7, 12, 13, 14, 19, 20, 21, 23, 26, 27, 28, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "306": {
    "question": "What restaurant hosts the October neighborhood luncheon in North Fayette on October 14, 2025?",
    "answer": "Bravo Italian Kitchen",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "307": {
    "question": "How much did Anthrocon 2024 contribute to Pittsburgh's local economy?",
    "answer": "$17.4 million.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "308": {
    "question": "Which hockey team plays at Covelli Centre on October 10, 2025?",
    "answer": "Youngstown Phantoms",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "309": {
    "question": "What brewery hosts the CMU alumni network happy hour on October 15, 2025?",
    "answer": "Hazel Grove Brewing",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "310": {
    "question": "What comedy show runs at Pittsburgh Improv starting October 10, 2025?",
    "answer": "Tony Roberts",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "311": {
    "question": "Where does the Cranberry Township neighborhood luncheon take place on October 17, 2025?",
    "answer": "Juniper Grill, 2030 MacKenzie Way Suite 800, Cranberry Township, PA 16066.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "312": {
    "question": "What Gilbert and Sullivan operetta is performed by Pittsburgh Savoyards in October 2025?",
    "answer": "Utopia, Limited",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "313": {
    "question": "What coffee event is scheduled in New York for October 18, 2025?",
    "answer": "Coffee Shop Speed Dating 40+, NYC (Lazy Sundaes, Brooklyn).",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "314": {
    "question": "When does Pittsburgh Opera perform La Boh\u00e8me in 2025?",
    "answer": "October 18, 21, 24, and 26, 2025. (pittsburghopera.org",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "315": {
    "question": "Which football team plays the Cleveland Browns on October 12, 2025?",
    "answer": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "316": {
    "question": "What venue hosts Jeff Daniels on October 10, 2025 at 7:30 PM?",
    "answer": "City Winery Pittsburgh",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "317": {
    "question": "What venue has a capacity of 2676 and hosts events in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "Heinz Hall",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "318": {
    "question": "When does Yippee Ki Yay (the Die Hard parody) run at Greer Cabaret Theater?",
    "answer": "December 2\ufffd?1, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "319": {
    "question": "At what time does Frzy's performance begin at Highmark First Night Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "10:45 p.m.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "320": {
    "question": "What is the venue for the Red Bull Turn It Up competition on October 17, 2025?",
    "answer": "Stage AE",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "321": {
    "question": "What haunted attraction at Cresson Prison runs through November 2, 2025?",
    "answer": "Imaginarium Sanitarium \ufffd?Haunted House",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "322": {
    "question": "What interactive comedy game show is happening at Arcade Comedy Theater on October 9, 2025 at 7:00 PM?",
    "answer": "PPWP Bracket Night Benefit",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "323": {
    "question": "What type of meditation session occurs weekly on Thursdays from 5:05-5:40 PM?",
    "answer": "Mid Week Recharge!",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "324": {
    "question": "What is Mark Godden's ballet featured in Pittsburgh Ballet Theatre's Spring Mix?",
    "answer": "Angels In The Architecture",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "325": {
    "question": "When does the Pittsburgh Symphony Orchestra perform Elf in Concert?",
    "answer": "Nov 21 2025 at 7:00 PM; Nov 23 2025 at 2:30 PM.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "326": {
    "question": "What type of event is planned for CMU alumni in Brooklyn on October 11, 2025?",
    "answer": "Whale and dolphin watching cruise.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "327": {
    "question": "Where is the Pittsburgh Irish Festival held?",
    "answer": "Carrie Blast Furnaces National Historic Landmark, 801 Carrie Furnace Blvd., Pittsburgh, PA 15218",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "328": {
    "question": "What concert fundraiser for Gaza takes place on November 1, 2025?",
    "answer": "Songs for Gaza \ufffd?Fundraising Concert for World Central Kitchen for Gaza Famine",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "329": {
    "question": "Which opera is performed at Pittsburgh Opera on October 18, 2025?",
    "answer": "La Boh\u00e8me",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "330": {
    "question": "What exhibition opens at the Posner Center on November 7, 2025?",
    "answer": "Rare Books & Ancestral Machines",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "331": {
    "question": "When does Tate McRae perform in Pittsburgh in 2025?",
    "answer": "October 15, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "332": {
    "question": "How much did Anthrocon 2025 raise for charity?",
    "answer": "$89,000 ",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "333": {
    "question": "What time does the free Electro Swing Party start on October 10, 2025?",
    "answer": "8:00 PM EDT",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "334": {
    "question": "What annual food drive runs from October 1 through November 8, 2025?",
    "answer": "Carnegie Mellon\u2019s 32nd Annual Food Drive",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "335": {
    "question": "Where can you see silhouette art being created on October 10, 2025 from 12-6 PM?",
    "answer": "love, Pittsburgh (489 Market St., Downtown)",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "336": {
    "question": "When does Playboi Carti perform in Pittsburgh in 2025?",
    "answer": "1-Nov-25",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "337": {
    "question": "What metal show features bands Thou, Cloud Rat, and Low Cunning on October 10, 2025?",
    "answer": "Thou / Cloud Rat / Low Cunning",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "338": {
    "question": "What is the name of the new hillclimb event introduced at PVGP in 2025?",
    "answer": "Motul Panther Hollow Hillclimb",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "339": {
    "question": "How long does the 2025 Phipps Spring Flower Show last?",
    "answer": "Four weeks.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "340": {
    "question": "When does Claire Rosinkranz perform at PPG Paints Arena?",
    "answer": "November 14, 2025 at 8:00 PM.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "341": {
    "question": "What is the new name of the circuit used for the 2025 PVGP races at Schenley Park?",
    "answer": "Schenley Oval",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "342": {
    "question": "What celebration takes place at the Warhol and Carnegie Museums on October 11, 2025?",
    "answer": "Hispanic Heritage Celebration",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "343": {
    "question": "What is the required pace per mile for Great Race participants?",
    "answer": "15 minutes per mile.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "344": {
    "question": "What are the dates for Les Mis\u00e9rables at the Benedum Center in Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "November 25\ufffd?0, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "345": {
    "question": "What No Doubt tribute show celebrates the 30th anniversary of which album on October 10, 2025?",
    "answer": "Tragic Kingdom",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "346": {
    "question": "What football team does Carnegie Mellon play against on November 8, 2025?",
    "answer": "Franklin & Marshall",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "347": {
    "question": "What is the theme for Phipps Spring Flower Show 2025?",
    "answer": "A Bloom for Every Room",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "348": {
    "question": "Which football teams play at Joe Walton Stadium on October 11, 2025?",
    "answer": "Robert Morris vs. Central Connecticut State.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "349": {
    "question": "On what dates will the Handmade Arcade Holiday Market take place in 2025?",
    "answer": "December 5\ufffd?, 2025",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "350": {
    "question": "How many Penguins home preseason games are at PPG Paints Arena in 2025?",
    "answer": "3",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "351": {
    "question": "What club hosts Jesse Roper on October 11, 2025 at 7:00 PM?",
    "answer": "Club Cafe",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "352": {
    "question": "What is the last day of CMU Fall 2025 Semester classes?",
    "answer": "5-Dec-25",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "353": {
    "question": "What musical runs from October 7-12, 2025 at the Benedum Center?",
    "answer": "SIX",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "354": {
    "question": "On what specific dates does CMU Thanksgiving Break occur in Fall 2025?",
    "answer": "November 26\ufffd?8, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "355": {
    "question": "What brewery hosts Cocktails with Kitties on October 10, 2025?",
    "answer": "Goodlander Cocktail Brewery",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "356": {
    "question": "How much has the Pittsburgh Vintage Grand Prix raised for charity since 1983?",
    "answer": "Over $7 million",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "357": {
    "question": "What is the length of the PVGP Panther Hollow Hillclimb course?",
    "answer": "1 mile",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "358": {
    "question": "What astronomy seminar features Adrian Price-Whelan on October 10, 2025 at noon?",
    "answer": "Astro Lunch Seminar",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "359": {
    "question": "What family attraction runs multiple dates and times starting October 10, 2025 at UPMC Events Center?",
    "answer": "Jurassic Quest",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "360": {
    "question": "What is the cap on total entrants for the Great Race as of 2015?",
    "answer": "16,500",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "361": {
    "question": "What musical celebrates the 70th anniversary on October 11, 2025?",
    "answer": "Oklahoma!",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "362": {
    "question": "Where can you get $60 flash tattoos every Friday in October 2025?",
    "answer": "Pittsburgh Tattoo & Piercing (Pittsburgh Tattoo Company), 103 Smithfield St., Downtown Pittsburgh.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "363": {
    "question": "What Irish music session takes place on the first Monday of every month?",
    "answer": "Traditional Irish Session Music at J. Gough\u2019s Tavern.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "364": {
    "question": "Which Fleetwood Mac tribute band performs at Silver Springs on October 11, 2025?",
    "answer": "True Rumours",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "365": {
    "question": "What rapper headlines Highmark First Night Pittsburgh 2025?",
    "answer": "Frzy",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "366": {
    "question": "What time do Pittsburgh Opera's Benedum Center performances start in the 2025-26 season?",
    "answer": "7:00 PM (evenings); 2:00 PM Sunday matinees \ufffd?except Falstaff\u2019s Sunday at 3:00 PM.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "367": {
    "question": "What is the suggested donation for attendees at the PVGP Schenley Park Race Weekend?",
    "answer": "$10 for the weekend",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "368": {
    "question": "Who is featured in the CMU student experience conversation on October 21, 2025?",
    "answer": "Gina Casalegno",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "369": {
    "question": "What was the attendance for Anthrocon 2025?",
    "answer": "18,357",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "370": {
    "question": "What is the theme for Phipps Fall Flower Show 2025?",
    "answer": "Visions of Japan",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "371": {
    "question": "Which Pittsburgh hockey team plays the New York Islanders on October 9, 2025?",
    "answer": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "372": {
    "question": "What are the dates for the Peoples Gas Holiday Market in 2025?",
    "answer": "November 21\u2013December 24, 2025 (closed Thanksgiving Day).",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "373": {
    "question": "What is the length of the UPMC Schenley Oval circuit at the PVGP?",
    "answer": "2 miles.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "374": {
    "question": "What happens to the Mini-1 term on October 10, 2025 at Carnegie Mellon?",
    "answer": "Mini-1 last day of classes",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "375": {
    "question": "What type of happy hour event is planned in Austin on October 21, 2025?",
    "answer": "Globally Plaid happy hour",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "376": {
    "question": "How many show cars are typically displayed at the PVGP International Car Show at Schenley Park?",
    "answer": "Around 3,000 show cars",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "377": {
    "question": "What is the name of the dance company performing on October 11, 2025 at 7:30 PM?",
    "answer": "Aakash Odedra Company",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "378": {
    "question": "What new feature was introduced at the 2025 Pittsburgh Irish Festival?",
    "answer": "Bodhr\u00e1n Blitz",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "379": {
    "question": "What Tepper webinar topic is scheduled for October 23, 2025?",
    "answer": "Breaking the Mold: Shaping the Future of Women-Owned Businesses",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "380": {
    "question": "Where does the 25th anniversary show \"Off the Record XXV: Burgh to the Future!\" take place on October 16, 2025?",
    "answer": "Byham Theater",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "381": {
    "question": "What venue hosts live music every Friday from 5-8 PM through October 24, 2025?",
    "answer": "The Strip District Terminal",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "382": {
    "question": "What venue hosts Tate McRae's Miss Possessive Tour on October 15, 2025?",
    "answer": "PPG Paints Arena",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "383": {
    "question": "What tribute band performs at Mr. Small's Theatre on October 10, 2025?",
    "answer": "No Doubt\u2019s Tragic Kingdom 30th Anniversary Tribute",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "384": {
    "question": "What two charities does the Pittsburgh Vintage Grand Prix primarily support?",
    "answer": "Autism Pittsburgh and Merakey Allegheny Valley School",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "385": {
    "question": "What drama production runs from October 8-10, 2025 at the Purnell Center?",
    "answer": "The House of Bernarda Alba",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "386": {
    "question": "When does A Musical Christmas Carol run at the Byham Theater?",
    "answer": "Dec 13\ufffd?3, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "387": {
    "question": "What are the specific dates for CMU's Fall 2025 final exams?",
    "answer": "December 8\ufffd?, 11\ufffd?2, and 14, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "388": {
    "question": "What online workshop about text analysis takes place on October 10, 2025 at 9:30 AM?",
    "answer": "Text Analysis in R: Exploring Banned Books",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "389": {
    "question": "When does Six the musical run at the Benedum Center?",
    "answer": "October 7\ufffd?2, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "390": {
    "question": "When was the Pittsburgh Great Race first established?",
    "answer": "1977",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "391": {
    "question": "Where can you take a historical walking tour on October 11, 2025 at 11:00 AM?",
    "answer": "Walk the Burgh Tours\ufffd?\u201cBest of the Burgh\ufffd?(1049 Penn Ave, Downtown Pittsburgh).",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "392": {
    "question": "When does Paul McCartney perform in Pittsburgh in 2025?",
    "answer": "November 11, 2025.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "393": {
    "question": "What is the price range for the First Night Friends VIP Experience at Highmark First Night Pittsburgh?",
    "answer": "$45\ufffd?200",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "394": {
    "question": "What type of dance competition takes place at Cohon University Center on October 11, 2025?",
    "answer": "Carnegie Classic ballroom Dancesport competition.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "395": {
    "question": "What celebration takes place during CMU's Homecoming Weekend from November 6-8, 2025?",
    "answer": "CMU125 \ufffd?Carnegie Mellon\u2019s 125th-anniversary \u201cPower of Possibilities\ufffd?celebration",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "396": {
    "question": "What theater production is titled \"Amanda: She Didn't Mean to Die\" on October 11, 2025?",
    "answer": "A.M. Wakeup Call\u2019s stage play at Edward W. Powers Auditorium (DeYor Performing Arts Center).",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "397": {
    "question": "Where can you attend Monday trivia from 7-9 PM through December 29, 2025?",
    "answer": "Spirit (242 51st St, Pittsburgh).",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "398": {
    "question": "What Halloween event features Tim Burton's classic at Heinz Hall on October 25-26, 2025?",
    "answer": "Tim Burton\u2019s The Nightmare Before Christmas in Concert.",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "399": {
    "question": "What Scottish event is planned for CMU alumni in Georgia on October 18, 2025?",
    "answer": "Scottish Festival at Stone Mountain",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  },
  "400": {
    "question": "What Pittsburgh soccer team plays on October 11, 2025?",
    "answer": "Pittsburgh Riverhounds SC",
    "source_doc_ids": []
  }
}